"迷失" 前情提要...
Previously on "Lost"...
臭丫头
Son of a bitch.
把枪放下!
我怀孕了...
我们马上送你去医院 Locke先生?
We're gonna get you to the hospital. Mr. Locke?
Locke先生?
Mr. Locke?
你弄清楚 他们藏在潜水艇上的东西了?
You found what they were hiding in the submarine?
一清二楚
I most certainly did.
啊!
Aah!
- 你好 Hugo  - 我们得跟你谈谈
- Hello, Hugo.  - We have to talk to you.
"我们"?
"We"?
好了 伙计们
Okay, guys.
出来吧
Come on out.
你好 Jack
Hello, Jack.
我正等着你呢
I was hoping you'd come.
我想 我们得好好叙叙旧呢
I think we have some catching up to do.
Hurley啊...
Hurley...
来见他是你的主意
This was your idea.
我跟他谈谈 没事吧?
You all right with me talking with him alone?
自己当心 伙计
It's all you, dude.
走吧 去谈吧
All right, let's catch up.
你这模样真像他
You look just like him.
没给你造成困扰吧?
Does it bother you?
不 让我困扰的是
No, what bothers me is
- 我根本不晓得你是什么东西  - 这倒是
- I don't have any idea what the hell you are.  - Sure you do.
为什么挑John Locke?
Why John Locke?
因为他笨得相信
Because he was stupid enough to believe
自己是基于某个理由 而到这儿来的
that he'd been brought here for a reason,
因为他对此始终坚信不疑 直到因此身亡
because he pursued that belief until it got him killed,
还因为你的善良
and because you were kind enough
用一具精致木棺 将他的遗体运载来此
to bring his body back here in a nice wooden box.
还因为你要扮成他 所以他必须得死吧
He had to be dead before you could look like him.
没错
That's right.
你还想扮成谁?
Who else have you looked like?
Jack 你到底想问我什么?
Jack, what do you really want to ask me?
我们到这儿来的第三天 我看见...
The third day we were here, I saw...
我在林间追逐我爸...
I chased my father through the jungle...
我... 已故的父亲
My... my dead father.
他也是你扮成的?
Was that you?
没错 是我
Yes, that was me.
为什么?
Why?
你需要找到水源
You needed to find water.
可能说出来你不信 Jack
This may be hard for you to believe, Jack,
但我所做的一切都是为了帮你
but all I've ever been interested in is helping you.
帮我?
Help me?
干嘛?
To do what?
离开这里
Leave.
因为Jacob选了你
But because Jacob chose you,
所以在你没来之前 你就已经注定要受困此岛
you were trapped on this island before you even got here.
但现在 Jacob死了
But now Jacob's dead.
我们再也不用被困在这儿了
We don't have to be trapped anymore.
我们可以登上飞机 想走就走
We can get on an airplane and fly away anytime we want to.
如果我们真的想走就能走
And if we can just fly away whenever we want,
那你为何还在这里?
why are you still here?
因为我得找齐所有人
Because it has to be all of us.
怎么了?
What?
我们当中 John Locke是唯一一个
John Locke was the only one of us
对该地抱有信仰的人
that ever believed in this place.
他竭尽全力
He did everything he could
阻止我们离岛
to keep us from leaving this island.
John Locke可不是个信徒 Jack
John Locke was not a believer, Jack.
他不过是个傻瓜
He was a sucker.
心率过速 当前值为130 血压持续降低
Sinus tach at 130, B.P. dropping.
最新数据62/30
Last read was 62 over 30,
- 可能由内出血造成  - 神经可有受损迹象?
- Possibly due to internal bleeding.  - Any signs of neurological damage?
下半身无反应
No response in lower reflexes.
- 因为他下半身瘫痪了  - 你认识他?
- That's because he's a paraplegic.  - You know this man?
嗯 他是我们学校的代课老师 他姓...
Yes. He's a substitute teacher at my school. His name is...
Locke 我们都称他Locke先生 我不知道他的名字
Locke. Mr. Locke. I don't know his first name.
但他有轮椅的 轮椅哪儿去了?
But he uses a wheelchair. Where is it?
早变成碎片了 搞不好是轮椅救了他一命
Smashed to pieces, that thing probably saved his life.
我看到了肇事者 就是那个逃逸司机
I saw the man that did this, the... the hit-and-run driver.
- 他... 他到过我们学校门口  - 等到了医院 你可以把这些告诉警察
- He... he was at our school.  - When we get to the hospital, you can talk to the cops.
- 你知道 这事我们该通知谁吗?  - 我不知道 我之前就说过 我跟他不是很熟
- But do you know anyone we can contact for him?  - I have no idea. Like I said, I barely know him.
- Helen  - 你说什么?
- Helen.  - What did you say?
通知Helen Norwood
Helen Norwood.
我本来打算... 娶她的
I was... gonna marry her.
呃...
Well...
你照样可以娶她啊
You're still gonna marry her
因为你会好起来的 Locke先生
'Cause you're gonna be okay, Mr. Locke.
叫我John
John.
我的名字叫John
My name is John.
钝击外伤患者 男性 年近50
Blunt force trauma victim, late 40s male,
- 他需要做CT扫描  - 枪伤患者 女性
- He needs a C.T. Scan.  - We got a gunshot wound here. Female.
- 射入伤... 伤口位于右上腹  - 孩子! 孩子!
- Entry wound... upper right quadrant.  - Baby! Baby!
嗯 先生 我明白的 她怀孕了
Yes, sir. I understand. She's pregnant.
- 我们会照顾好她的  - 孩子!
- We're gonna take good care of her.  - Baby!
- 有外出血现象 失血量500cc  - 孩子!
- 500 lost CC'S. External blood loss.  - Baby!
我们会尽力救治的
We're gonna do everything we can.
不... 不!
Sun... 怎么了?
是他!
怎么了?
What is it?
出来吧
You can come out.
你一直在跟踪我们 Claire?
You following us, Claire?
没错
Yeah.
为什么?
Why?
因为他是我哥哥
'Cause he's my brother.
看来 你们有很多话要说啊
Looks like you two have a lot of catching up to do.
我不打扰你们了
I'll leave you to it.
Claire 对... 对不起...
Claire, I'm... I'm so sorry th...
他告诉你了吗?
Did he tell you?
他就是那个假装我们父亲的人?
That he was the one pretending to be our father?
是的
Yeah.
是的 他告诉我了
Yeah, he told me.
我几乎已经不指望
You know, I pretty much gave up hoping
你会回来了
that you'd ever come back.
既然你来了...
Now that you're here...
很... 很高兴见到你 Jack
It's...it's good to see you, Jack.
我也很高兴见到你
Yeah, it's good to see you, too.
我... 我从来没有感受过家庭的温存
You know, I... I never really had much in the way of family,
所以... 你能和我们在一起 这意义非同一般
So it... really means a lot that you're coming with us.
其实 我还... 拿不定主意 要不要和你们在一起
Actually, I haven't... I haven't decided if I'm coming with you.
不 你已经决定了
Yeah, you have.
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
你让他和你说话的时候 就已经决定好了
You decided the moment you let him talk to you,
就和我们一样
Just like the rest of us.
就这么回事
So, yeah,
无论你喜不喜欢
Whether you like it or not,
你现在都和他在一起了
you're with him now.
迷失 第6季第13集
他有一艘潜艇?
He's got a submarine?
小声点 该死的
Keep your voice down, damn it.
没错 Widmore有一艘潜艇
Yeah, Widmore's got a sub.
- 我们可以用它来离开这个岛  - 要告诉Sun吗?
- We're using it to get off this rock.  - Are we gonna tell Sun?
Kate正在和她说
Kate's telling her now.
我觉得我们要避免乱成一团
I thought we might want to avoid huddles.
那Sayid呢?
What about Sayid?
没算上Sayid 他变坏了
Sayid ain't invited. He's gone over to the dark side.
没错 但你总能让别人弃恶从善
Yeah, but you can always bring people back from the dark side.
- 我是说 Anakin...  - Anakin是谁?
- I mean, Anakin...  - Who the hell's Anakin?
听着 闭上你的嘴 对其他人要只字不提
Look, just keep your mouth shut. Don't say nothin' to no one.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 Claire
Hey, Claire.
嘿 Hurley
Hey, Hurley.
你气色不错哦
You look great.
大家又重新聚在一起了 真是太棒了
It's so nice to have everyone back together again.
想吃苹果吗?
Want an apple?
嘿 Schaub 是我带她来这儿的
Hey, Schaub, I'm the one who brought her in.
能让我们单独待会儿吗?
Wanna give us a minute?
Katherine Anne Austen因纵火
Katherine Anne Austen.Wanted for arson,
和袭击联邦官员
assault on a federal officer,
以一级谋杀罪被通缉
murder in the first degree.
真有意思 你打我的样子 可不像是一个谋杀犯啊
Funny. You don't strike me as the murdering kind.
那是因为我不是啊
That's because I'm not.
等联邦干探来的时候 你可以把这话告诉他们
You be sure and mention that to Feds when they get here.
你到底想干嘛?
There something you wanted?
还记得我吗? 在机场的时候?
You remember me? From the airport?
我们坐的同一个从悉尼回来的航班
We were on the same flight from Sydney.
是的 我记得
Yeah, I remember.
你不觉得这有点奇怪吗...
Well, don't you think it's weird...
你和我坐的同一个航班
You and me being on the same flight,
又在电梯里偶遇?
having that little meet-up in the elevator?
一周后... 砰
And a week later... boom.
洛杉矶有那么多汽车 你偏偏撞到了我的车
Of all the cars in Los Angeles, you smash into mine.
就像有人要把我们拴在一块儿
Almost like someone's trying to put us together.
你在跟我搭讪吗?
Are you hitting on me?
没可能的 宝贝
It'd never work, sweetheart.
- 我是个警察 你是个杀人犯...  - 我跟你说过了 我不是杀人犯
- I'm a cop. You're a murderer...  - I already told you. I'm not a murderer.
好吧 但我还是警察啊
Yeah, well, I'm still a cop.
那你为什么不抓我呢?
So why didn't you arrest me?
我已经抓住你了
I did arrest you.
不 在洛杉矶国际机场的电梯里
No, in L.A.X., the elevator.
你看见我带着手铐
You saw I was wearing handcuffs.
我没看到有什么手铐啊
I didn't see any handcuffs.
我只看到了
All I saw was
一个想要人帮忙开门的美女
a pretty lady who needed the door held open for her.
你知道我在想什么吗?
You know what I think?
我觉得你放了我 是因为你去过澳大利亚
I think you let me go because you went to Australia,
但你又不想让别人知道你去了那儿
and you didn't want anyone to know you were there.
当联邦干探来的时候 我该把这告诉他们吗?
Should I tell that to the Feds when they get here?
- 哦 我喜欢你  - 哦
- Oh, I like you.  - Oh.
Jim 抓到了一个活的 快点
Jim. Got a live one. Come on.
对不起
Sorry.
有任务
Duty calls.
有家饭店发生了一桩多人凶杀案 我们正介入调查中
We caught a multiple homicide at a restaurant.
死者是一名叫Keamy的歹徒
Victims were a lowlife named Keamy
还有他三名手下
and three goons on his payroll.
现场有一名韩国女子中弹
Korean female G.S.W. at the scene,
她的男友目击了一切 但他不会说英语
and her boyfriend witnessed it, but he doesn't speak English.
有嫌疑人的消息吗?
Any suspects?
是的 一台ATM机上的探头
Yeah, an A.T.M. surveillance camera
拍到了这个家伙逃离现场的画面
grabbed this jaboney fleeing the scene.
很好 查一下这个人叫什么
All righty. Put a name to that face.
那就是我们要抓的人
That's our bad guy.
他变了
He's different now.
我想我们都变了
Guess we're all different now.
Locke跟你说了什么?
So what did Locke say to you?
他说他想要离开这儿
He said that he wants to leave,
而且我们必须一起走
and we all have to go together.
- 你相信他吗?  - 我不知道
- And do you believe him?  - I'm not sure yet.
举起手来
Hands up.
不许动
Stop right there.
管事的人呢?
Where's the man in charge?
她是谁?
Who's she?
她是Widmore的副手
That's Widmore's Number Two.
有什么可以帮忙的吗?
What can I do for ya?
你从我们这儿拿了点东西 我们想要回来
You took something from us, and we want it back.
对不起 我不知道你在说些什么
I'm sorry. I don't know what you're talking about.
稍安勿躁
It's Okay.
- 确定我的位置了吗?  - 定位完毕
- Do you have a fix on my position?  - Roger that.
让他们看看我们的本事
Show them what we're capable of.
傍晚之前 把你拿走的东西还回来
You have until nightfall to return what you took.
否则 下次射中的就是你们了
or next time, we won't miss.
准备好让我们来接他的时候 给我打电话
Call me when you're ready for us to pick him up.
那么...
Well...
我们开干吧
Here we go.
嗯 嗨 我和西太平洋收养局
Uh, hi. I have an appointment
有个预约
with the Western Pacific Adoption Agency.
在十五楼 请先签字登记
15th floor. And sign in, please.
好的
Sure.
你好
Hey there.
你好吗?
How are you?
嗯 我们在机场见过吗... 在 嗯 行李领取处
Uh, we met at the airport... the, uh, the baggage claim.
哦 对 嗨
Oh, yeah. Hi.
嗨 我是Desmond 全名是Desmond Hume
Hi. I'm Desmond. Desmond Hume.
嗯 我还不知道你的名字 嗯...
Um, I never got your name. Uh...
"Claire Littleton"啊
"Claire Littleton."
嗯... 你最近怎么样?
So... so how you doin'?
嗯 我很好 现在好多了 之前略有受惊
Um, I'm okay. Better now. I actually had a bit of a scare.
- 结果进了医院  - 哦 不 抱歉一问 你...
- Ended up in the hospital.  - Oh, no. I'm sorry. Are you...
哦 不 现在都没事了 所以...
Oh, no. It's all good now, so...
哦 顺便说一句 嗯 你猜对了
Oh, by the way, uh, you were right.
是个男孩
It's a boy.
我对这方面的感觉异常灵敏
I have a nose for these things.
我说 嗯...
Look, um...
抱歉 我想问一个私人点的问题 嗯
Excuse me if this sounds a bit personal, but, um,
我无意间发现
I couldn't help noticing
你要去收养局... 而且独自一人去
you're going to an adoption agency... alone.
嗯... 对 你说得对 这是个私人问题
Uh... Yeah. You're right. It is personal.
不 我是说 你应该找个... 代表律师
No, I just meant you should have some... some legal representation.
什么 你是律师?
What, are you a lawyer?
不 不是
No. No.
但是 嗯 我正好要去见一位律师
But, uh, it just so happens that I'm on my way to see one.
你知道 收养合同很麻烦
You know, adoption contracts are complicated.
你该留神点儿
And you should be careful
因为你可能会陷入麻烦
because you could find yourself in a situation
而且永无宁日
that's irreversible.
问题是 我... 我没钱请律师
Yeah, I... I don't have money for a lawyer.
到几楼?
What floor?
嗯... 我... 我也要去十五喽
Um... I'm... I'm going to 15 as well.
听我说 这位 嗯 我要见的这位律师... 她很出色
Look, this, um, this attorney I'm seeing... she's excellent.
嗯 还有 她欠我一个人情
Uh, you know, plus, she owes me a favor.
所以...
So...
你为什么不去见见她呢?
Why don't you just come and meet her?
况且 我觉得她能给你实际帮助
You know, I think she could really help you.
我保证
Look, I promise you,
不花你一分钱
It won't cost you a cent.
拜托
Please.
能帮到你的话 我万分高兴
It'd be my absolute pleasure.
嗯 好吧
Uh, sure.
太好了 这边请
Great. This way.
谢谢
Thanks.
嗨 嗯 我是Desmond Hume 来见Verdansky女士 麻烦你
Hi. Uh, Desmond Hume to see Ms. Verdansky, please.
哦 是的 Hume先生 她在等你
Oh, yes. Mr. Hume. She's expecting you.
- 请坐  - 好
- Have a seat.  - Great.
嗨 嗯... 谢谢
Hey, um... Thank you.
不客气
You're very welcome.
Desmond啊
Desmond!
啊 Ilana
Ah, Ilana.
嗯 Claire 这位是Ilana
Uh, Claire, this is Ilana.
Ilana 这位是我的朋友
Ilana, I'd like you to meet a friend of mine,
- Claire littleton  - 呃...
- Claire littleton.  - Um...
我真希望你能够帮助她
I was hoping you'd be able to help her.
冒昧问下
I'm sorry.
你叫Claire Littleton 从澳大利亚来?
Claire Littleton from Australia?
呃 我们认识吗?
Um, do I know you?
不 但这是个巧合
No, but this is quite a coincidence.
我们一直都在找你呢
We've been looking for you.
Desmond 可以让我和Littleton女士单独
Desmond, do you mind if I speak with Ms. Littleton alone
聊几分钟吗?
for a few minutes?
当然 没问题的 去聊吧
No. Absolutely fine. Go right ahead.
大家听着
Listen up, everyone.
嗨
Hey.
出什么事儿了?
What's going on?
那些人又想要杀我们
People are trying to kill us again.
这事出乎我意料之外
All this is happening a bit sooner than I'd expected,
这些人胁迫我们
but these people have forced our hand,
口口声声说 我们偷了他们的东西
claiming we stole something from them,
想要挑事
trying to provoke us into a confrontation.
如果他们想打 那我们就打
Well, if that's what they want, that's what they'll get.
拿上你们的东西
Gather your things.
我们要到另一个岛去 然后登上那架飞机
We're going to the other island and we're getting on that plane.
James 我需要你帮我点忙
James, I need your help with something.
有艘船停在
There's a boat moored
离这数小时路程外的海岸边
just a few hours down the shore from here.
我要你去弄来 然后跟我们
I want you to get it and meet the rest of us
在断崖的另一头会合
on the other side of these bluffs.
我们大家一起划船去另一个岛
We'll all sail over to the other island together.
- 你能办到吗 James?  - 为什么我们不一起去弄船?
- Can you do that, James?  - How come we're not all heading for it together?
人越多 办起事来越麻烦
The bigger the group, the slower it moves.
- 好吧 我需要个帮手  - 随你挑
- All right. I could use another pair of hands.  - Take whoever you want.
怎么样 雀斑女? 你知道怎么划桨吗?
How about it, Freckles? Know anything about sailing?
知道
I know enough.
好的 我们等着你们 Sayid 你有空吗?
Good. We'll be waitin' for ya. Sayid, you got a minute?
能帮我个忙吗?
Can you give me a hand with somethin'?
听着 我只说一遍
Listen up, 'cause I'm only gonna say this once.
我们不到集合地点去接Locke
We're not going to that rendezvous point
我和Widmore做了个交易
to pick up Locke. I got a deal with Widmore.
是什么交易?
What kind of deal?
听我说 只要一有机会
Just listen. First chance you get,
你就折回来 到这个地点
You double back, hoof it to this spot.
这儿有一个废弃的码头
There's an old dock.
拽上Hugo Sun 和Lapidus Kate和我会在那儿跟你们会合
Grab Hugo, Sun and Lapidus. Kate and I will meet you there.
那Sayid和Claire呢?
What about Sayid and Claire?
Sayid就是个傀儡 Claire疯疯癫癫的
Sayid's a zombie and Claire's nuts.
从她想杀Kate的那一刻起 飞机上就没她的位置了
She gave up her ticket when she tried to kill kate,
而且我不会再让她有机会对Kate下手了
and I ain't gonna let that happen again.
叫上Hugo Sun 和那个飞行员 只有这些人 明白吗?
That's Hugo, Sun and the pilot. Only them. Understand?
但是我怎么带大家从... 从Locke的眼皮底下离开?
But how am I supposed to get us away from... from Locke?
你自己想办法
You figure it out.
准备开路了吗?
Ready to roll?
- 刚才那是怎么回事?  - 男人间的对话
- What was that all about?  - Guy talk.
我要你去我处理Desmond的地方
I need you to go out to where I've got Desmond.
我以为你不打算让他活着回来了
I thought you weren't going to give him back.
我的确有这打算
I'm not.
我要你去杀了他
You're gonna kill him.
这不会有什么问题的 对吧 Sayid?
And that's not gonna be a problem, is it, Sayid?
你仍想要我做成那件答应你的事 对吗?
You do still want what you asked me for, right?
是的 我想
Yes, I do.
那就按我说的做
Then go do what I said.
如果你要冷血地把我干掉 兄弟...
If you're gonna shoot me in cold blood, brother...
我觉得我有权知道
I think I have a right to know
你能得到什么
what you're gettin' in exchange for it.
他告诉我 我可以找回我失去的一些东西
He told me I could get something back I lost.
那你失去了什么?
And what did you lose?
我爱的女人
The woman I loved.
她现在在哪儿?
And where is she now?
她死了
Dead.
你凭什么觉得Locke可以把她带回来?
And what makes you think Locke can bring her back?
我死过一次...
I died...
他把我救活了
And he brought me back.
那你怎么对她说?
So what will you tell her?
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
这个女人...
This woman...
当她问你 你是怎么才和她重聚的...
when she asks you what you did to be with her again...
你怎么对她说?
what will you tell her?
Sayid啊
Sayid.
出什么事儿了?
What's going on?
现在你一身轻松了
Everything will be okay for you now.
我处理好了
I took care of it.
你什么意思? 你去哪儿?
What do you mean? Where are you going?
我得走了
I have to leave.
你伤人了吗?
Did you hurt someone?
Nadia 我要走了
Nadia, I'm leaving,
我永远也不能再回来了
and I'm never going to be able to come back again.
你干了什么 Sayid?
What did you do, Sayid?
拖住他们
Stall them.
是谁?
Who is it?
洛杉矶警察局
L.A.P.D.
我能看看证件吗?
May I see some identification?
请你把门打开 可以吗?
Can you open the door, please?
Jarrah夫人 我是Straume探员
Mrs. Jarrah, I'm detective Straume.
我要问你几个问题
I need to ask you some questions.
你有时间吗?
You have a few minutes?
好的 趴下
That's good. Stay down.
Sayid Jarrah啊?
Sayid Jarrah?
你被捕了
You're under arrest.
船被吹到那儿了
There she blows.
准备好沾水了吗?
You ready to get wet?
哦
Oh.
你确定这是个好主意吗?
You sure this is a good idea?
你看见桥了吗?
You see a bridge?
- 回去接Locke  - 当然不是
- Going back to get Locke.  - Of course not.
这是个烂点子 所以我们不会那么做
It's a terrible idea, which is why we ain't doing it.
什么?
What?
我们要甩下Locke
We're gonna ditch Locke.
你 我 Jack Hurley Sun 还有那个长得像
You, me, Jack, Hurley, Sun and that pilot that looks like
Burt Reynolds电影里某角色的飞行员
he's stepped off the set of a Burt Reynolds' movie.
你当初打算瞒我到什么时候?
When were you planning on telling me this?
就现在
Now.
等等 你没说Claire
Wait. You didn't say Claire.
因为没算上她
'Cause she ain't comin'.
你回岛上想找的那个Claire 已经不在了
The Claire you came back for is gone.
我保证过 要把她带回去
I promised I would bring her back.
那是在Claire投靠Locke之前
That was before she started drinkin' Locke's Kool-Aid.
她很危险 你真的想让她待在Aaron身边吗?
She's dangerous. You really want her around Aaron?
我们走 时间不多了
Let's go. We ain't got much time.
嗨 Claire
Hey, Claire.
嗨 Jack
Jack.
你跟着Locke多久了?
How long have you been with Locke?
从你们离开的时候起
Ever since you left.
那么你信任他?
So you trust him?
对
Yeah.
为什么?
Why?
因为他是唯一一个没有抛弃我的人
'Cause he's the only one that didn't abandon me.
Sun 你看见Sayid了吗?
Sun, have you seen Sayid?
在半英里前的地方 他就应该追上咱们了
He was supposed to catch up with us about a half a mile back.
哦 沉默不语?
Oh, the silent treatment?
都是你害的!
对不起 Sun 但是我什么也没做
I'm sorry, Sun, but I didn't do anything to you.
James现在应该在路上
James should be on his way by now.
让大家继续向海滩的方向走
Just keep everyone moving to the beach.
- 一会儿我会追上你们的  - 你去哪儿?
- I'll catch up with you there.  - Where are you going?
我要确保没人落下
I wanna make sure nobody got left behind.
- Hurley 等一下  - 怎么了?
- Hurley, wait up.  - Yeah?
Sun啊
Sun.
我们现在就得走
We have to go now.
去哪儿?
Go where?
没时间解释了 我们得走了 跟我来
There's no time. We just gotta go. Follow me.
嗯 我觉得我们应该按照Sawyer的计划行事
Um, I think we should stick to Sawyer's plan,
- 要不他会很生气  - 这就是Sawyer的计划 我们走
- or he'll be really pissed.  - This is Sawyer's plan. Let's go.
Sayid啊?
Sayid?
你去哪儿了?
Where have you been?
按你的吩咐 干活儿去了
Doing what you asked.
怎么那么长时间?
Then what took you so long?
我刚杀了一个手无缚鸡之力的人
I just shot an unarmed man.
我需要时间想想
I needed a moment.
Sayid 你杀了他吗?
Did you kill him, Sayid?
当然
Of course I did.
要是不信 你自己去看
Go and check, if you like.
快点儿 我们要赶船
Come on. We have a boat to catch.
我希望你知道目的地
I hope you know where you're going,
因为那个烟怪
'cause that smoke thing
比我们跑得快多了
runs a hell of a lot faster than we do.
- Sawyer 说这儿有个码头  - 在那儿!
- Sawyer said there'd be a dock around here somewhere.  - There they are!
嘿
Hey.
太棒了 我们走 大家上船 快点!
All right. Let's go. Everybody onboard. Let's go!
- 我们开这船回家?  - 不可能的 这设备不行
- We sailin' home on this, huh?  - Won't work, not without a bearing.
三年来 达摩组织成员都是
For three years, the only way Dharma folk
乘潜水艇进进出出
ever got on or off this island was by sub,
我们也要这么做 干得漂亮 医生
so that's what we're doing. Nice job, doc.
啊噢
Uh-oh.
你们去哪儿?
Where you going?
Claire啊
Claire...
没事儿
It's okay.
Kate啊
Kate.
我们要离开小岛
We're leaving the island.
那你们为什么不等John?
Then, uh, why aren't you waiting for John?
因为他不是John
Because that's not John,
不论他是谁 他不是我们的人
and whoever he is, he's not one of us.
Claire啊...
Claire...
跟我们走
come with us.
我能让你回到Aaron身边
I can get you back to Aaron.
- 等一下...  - Sawyer 闭嘴 她要不去 我也不去
- Wait a damn min...  - Sawyer, shut up. She is coming or I'm not.
Claire 跟我们走吧
Come with us, Claire.
- John向我保证...  - 不 我现在向你保证
- John promised me...  - No, I'm promising you.
他出生的时候 我就在现场
I was there when he was born.
他不应该由我来抚养
And I never should've raised him.
该抚养他的人 是你
It should've been you.
我是回来找你的 如此你们就可以团聚了
I came back to get you so you could be with him again.
Claire 这是我回来的唯一理由
It's the only reason I came back to the island, Claire.
所以 请跟我们走
So, please, come with us.
我们回家吧
Let's go home.
好吧 在Locke找来之前 快上船
All right. Get on the boat before Locke gets here.
他要是发现我们走了...
If he finds out we're gone...
他会很生气的
he's gonna be mad.
是你妈妈
It's your mom.
嘿
Hey.
是的 我们刚到
Yeah, we just got here.
谢谢
Thank you.
呃... 我不知道
Uh... I don't know.
我会让他尽快回家 5点吧?
I'll have him home as soon as I can. Maybe, like, 5:00?
其实 我们完事后要吃个饭
Actually, um, we might grab a bite to eat afterwards.
所以 呃 7点吧?
So, uh... maybe more like 7:00?
好吧
All right.
对
Yeah.
好 我会送他回去
Yeah, I'll drop him off.
嘿
Hey.
你知道
You know,
听你祖父的遗愿
hearing your grandfather's will being read,
不是件好玩的事 但...
I know it's not the most fun, but...
很快就完了 我保证
it'll be over soon, I promise.
还有... 悲伤点没关系
And it's... it's okay to be sad.
我是为你而悲伤 爸爸
I'm sad for you, dad.
走吧
Let's go.
Shephard先生
Mr. Shephard.
你好
Hello.
- 你肯定就是David了  - 你好
- And you must be David.  - Hi.
我们的会议室准备好了
We're set up in the conference room.
我有个惊喜给你
I've got a surprise for you.
你相信命运吗?
Do you believe in fate?
这是Claire Littleton
This is Claire Littleton.
Claire 这是Shephard先生 这是他的儿子 David
Claire, this is Mr. Shephard and his son David.
你好
Hello.
我... 我是Jack Shephard
I'm... I'm Jack Shephard.
嗨 很高兴见到你
Hi, it's, uh, it's really nice to meet you.
你找到她了
You found her.
实际上 是她找到我们的
Actually, she found us.
呃...
Uh...
我父亲的遗嘱里 有你的名字
you were in my father's will.
你介意告诉我 你是怎么认识他的吗?
Do you mind if I ask you how you knew him?
他也是我爸爸
He was my father, too.
抱歉 我接个电话
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
这是 呃 医院打来的
This is the, uh, this is the service.
对 我是Shephard医生
Yeah, this is Dr. Shephard.
不 不 现在不方便
No, no, it's not a very good time.
对 他们可以为他安排手术了
Yes, they can go ahead and prep him.
我20分钟到
I'm 20 minutes away.
抱歉 医院里有急诊
I'm so sorry. There's been an emergency at the hospital,
还有 呃...
and, um...
我们要再约时间了
We're gonna have to reschedule.
船长 我知道我问得有点儿晚
I know I'm a little late to the party, Captain,
但你介意告诉我 你的游玩计划吗?
but you mind filling us in on what your game plan is?
胸肌男 我的计划就是到九头蛇岛上去
My plan, chesty, is to land on Hydra Island,
跟Widmore拉拉近乎
Get ourselves nice and cuddly with Widmore
这样我们就有机会上潜水艇了
until we get a chance to jump on that sub.
然后我就拿枪逼着一个人
Then I'm gonna put a gun in someone's face
让他带我们回家
and make 'em take us home.
我喜欢这主意
I like that idea.
我看见船舱里有些罐头
I saw some canned food down in the galley.
有人饿了吗?
Anybody else starvin'?
雀斑女 过来掌会儿舵?
Freckles. Take the wheel a minute?
好的
Sure.
温柔点
Be nice.
好的 知道了
Yeah, yeah.
没有想到你会出现 医生
Didn't think you'd show up, doc.
什么?
Sorry?
你可不是个唯命是从的人
Taking orders ain't your strong suit.
很开心 最后还是见到你了
Nice to see you finally came around.
感觉有些不对
This doesn't feel right.
感觉什么不对呢?
What doesn't feel right?
离开这个岛
Leaving the island.
你想告诉我为什么不要离开吗?
You wanna tell me why not?
因为我仍然清晰地记得 我上次离开时的感受...
Because I remember how I felt last time I left...
感觉像是失去了部分自我
Like a part of me was missing.
他们有治那种幻觉的药 医生
They got pills for that, doc.
我们之所以被带到这里
We were brought here
是因为 我们注定要来这里做些什么的 James
because we're supposed to do something. James.
还有 如果Locke... 那个... 那个东西...
And if Locke... that... that thing...
想要我们离开呢?
wants us to leave?
如果我们留在岛上 或许会发生令它害怕的事吧
Maybe it's afraid of what happens if we stay.
滚下我的船去
Get off my damn boat.
什么?
What?
是时候做出抉择了
You got a decision to make and you make it now.
要不你跟着我们
Either you're with us,
继续对自己说这些疯话
you keep that damn crazy talk to yourself,
- 要不你就跳到海里去  - James 这样做是不对的
- or you're going in the water.  - James, this is a mistake.
而且我知道 你或多或少 也有这种感觉
And I know there's a part of you that feels that.
这个岛和我们还没完呢
The island is not done with us yet.
是呢 呃 但是我和这个岛已经玩完了
Yeah, well, I'm done with this island.
所以如果你执着于你的感受 Jack 那你就那么做吧
So if you wanna take a leap of faith, Jack, then take it.
滚下我的船去
Get off my damn boat.
对于Juliet因我而死 我真的很抱歉
I'm sorry that I got Juliet killed.
Jack啊?!
Jack?!
- 你都和他说什么了?  - 他现在反悔了
- What did you say to him?  - He changed his mind.
他反悔了 什么意思?!
What do you mean, he changed his mind?!
- 你都和他说了些什么?  - 他不跟我们一起走了
- What did you say to him?!  - He ain't comin' with us.
我们必须回去救他上来
We have to go back and get him.
我们不能再回头了 Kate
We're done going back, Kate.
Jin啊?
你醒了喔
发生什么事了?
你中弹了
但是你会好起来的...
那咱们的孩子呢?
孩子很好
都结束了...
我们都会好起来的
所以这些年来
So all these years,
你根本不知道爷爷有另外一个孩子?
you had no idea your dad had another kid?
不 根本不知道
Nope. None.
哇哦 我无法想象他居然从未提及过她
Wow. I can't believe he never even mentioned her.
是呢 呃 你爷爷有好多的秘密呢
Yeah, well, your grandfather kept a lot of things to himself.
是你自己这么觉得吧?
Is that where you get it from?
可能是吧
Yeah, probably.
好的 呃...
All right. Uh...
- 你一个人在这里待会儿 没问题吧?  - 呃 好的 没问题
- You gonna be okay hangin' while I do this?  - Uh, yeah, sure.
祝你好运 爸爸
Good luck, dad.
谢谢你
Thanks.
被车撞了的路人
Car V. Ped.
有多糟糕呢?
How bad?
很糟糕
Bad.
还有件麻烦事...
But here's the kicker...
伤者本来就下半身瘫痪
The victim was already in a wheelchair.
已存在脊椎问题
Preexisting spinal condition.
硬脊膜囊封塞
Dural sac's obliterated.
所以我们才喊你过来 我们已经焦头烂额了
That's why we called you. We're in a bit over our heads here.
没事
Yeah.
交给我了
I got this.
- 准备好开刀了吗?  - 随时候命
- We ready to cut?  - Say the word.
手术刀
Scalpel.
怎么了?
What is it?
我想我认识这个人
I think I know this guy.
这天气太适合游泳了
Nice day for a swim.
Sawyer开走了我的船 对吧?
Sawyer took my boat, didn't he?
是的
Yeah.
大家都靠拢些 营地在这边
Everybody stay close. The camp's over here.
Locke很快就会知道
We're not gonna have much time
我们开走了他的船
before Locke's figured out we made off with his ride.
- 把手举起来!  - 嘿! 哇!
- Hands up!  - Hey! Whoa!
- 哇哦! 冷静!  - 放下枪! 放下!
- Whoa! Take it easy!  - Drop your weapons! Drop 'em!
放下枪!
Drop 'em now!
没事了 我认识他
It's all right. I know him.
还有谁和你一起来的?
Who else is with you?
没别人了! 如果你是想知道Locke在哪里
Nobody! If you're wondering where Locke is,
他现在还在主岛呢
he's still back on the main island.
防御解除
Turn the fences off.
Ford和他的五个朋友刚乘船到岸
Ford just showed up on a boat with five of his friends.
Sun吗?
Sun?
Jin啊?
Jin?
- 是Jin!  - Sun!
- Jin!  - Sun!
我爱你
I love you.
我也好爱你
I love you, too.
我从未停止过寻找你
I never stopped looking for you.
貌似某些人又可以说英语了
Looks like someone got their voice back.
我们再也不会分开了
We'll never be apart again.
我向你保证
I promise you.
你确定吗?
Are you sure?
我... 我明白了 Charles
I... I understand, Charles.
Widmore吗?
That Widmore?
你在搞什么呀?
What the hell are you doin'?
我像是在干什么呢? 把手举起来
What's it look like I'm doin'? Hands up now.
所有人都跪在地上!
On your knees, all of you!
跪下!
Down!
- 我们有过协议的  - 协议终止了
- We had a deal!  - Deal's off.
我搞定他们了
We got 'em.
- 看见Locke 杀无赦  - 收到
- If you've got a sightline on Locke, fire when ready.  - Roger.
卧倒!
Get down!
Jack? 你还好吗?
Jack? You all right?
别担心 会好起来的
Don't worry. It's gonna be okay.
我会陪着你的
You're with me now.